A Finding Aid to the Fischbach Gallery Records, 1937-2015, bulk 1963-1977, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fiscgall
Archives of American Art
- Addition to the Fischbach Gallery Records, circa 1960s-2015; Series 7; 14 Linear feet Box 29-42
  - Inventory Card Indexes, circa 1960s-2015; 7.1; 12.1 Linear feet Box 29-41
    - Second A-Z Sequence, circa 1960s-2015; 7.1.2; 7.3 Linear feet Box 33-41
      - Moore, John, 1969-1984 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Nelson, Jud, circa 1990s (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Nicholson, Ana Maria, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Nick, George, 1985-2003 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Ohlson, Doug, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Osborne, Elizabeth, 1978-1988 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
      - Paquette, Thomas, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Parker, Ray, 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Pavlos, circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Pearson, John, circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Pfahler, Georg Karl, circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Plansky, Carl, 2002-2009 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Polinskie, Kenneth, 1983-1988 (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
      - Porter, Fairfield, circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Portnow, Marjorie, 1985-1988 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Ruddick, Dorothy, circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Ryan, Anne, circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Ryman, Robert, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - R, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Saunders, David, 2000-2004 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Scott, Amy Finley, 1981-1991 (Box 39, Folder 22-23)
      - Shatter, Susan, 1972-1996 (Box 39, Folder 24-26)
      - Shileds, Meg, 1999-2007 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Shorr, Harriet, 1977-1986 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Shostak, Ed, circa 1971 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Slavin, Arlene, 1972-1974; 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Slonem, Hunt, circa 1977 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Smith, Tony, circa 1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Snowden, Mary, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Sugarman, George, circa 1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Sullivan, Billy, 1985-2001 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
      - Sultan, Altoon, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Supplee, Sarah, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Swain, Robert, circa 1968 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - S, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Tarlow, Philip, 1979-1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Tavarelli, Andrew, 1972-1977 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Touchton, Jim, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
      - Townsend, Diane, circa 1982 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Vagliano (Pettus), Sally, circa 1977 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Vicente, Esteban, circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Waid, Mary Joan, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Walp, Susan Jane, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Weidle, Jim, 1981-1986 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Welliver, Neil, 1974-1981 (Box 40, Folder 21-22)
      - Wexler, George, 1982-1999 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Widmier, Hank, circa 1973 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Wilson, Douglas Fenn, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Wilson, Jane, 1976-1997 (Box 40, Folder 26-28)
      - Winkfield, Trevor, 1971-1976 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Winter, Roger, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Workman, Mark, circa 1990s (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Yates, Sharon, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Young, Cole, 1983-1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Client Sales Card Index, circa 1970s-2000s; 7.2; 1.9 Linear feet Box 41-42
    The client sales card index dates from circa 1970s-2000s and includes index cards containing the date, title, and price of works sold, organized by client name.
    - A, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
    - B, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
    - C, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 7-8)
    - D, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - E, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - F, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
    - G, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 13-14)
    - H, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
    - I, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - J, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - K, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - L, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - M, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
    - Mc, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - N, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - O, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - P, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
    - Q, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - R, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 11-12)
    - S, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 13-14)
    - T, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - U, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - V, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - W, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 18-19)
    - X, Y, Z, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 20)